<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <LetterShamblerSwarmArrived>A group of {0} shambling, rotting corpses is approaching. Some inhuman force has reanimated these lifeless bodies and set them to murder.\n\nThey will now wander through the area. If they see a human, they will attack. If not, they will leave in a few days.\n\nIf you can capture one, you can study it for dark knowledge.</LetterShamblerSwarmArrived>
  <LetterShamblerArrived>A shambling, rotting corpse is approaching. Some inhuman force has reanimated this lifeless body and set it to murder.\n\nIt will now wander through the area. If it sees a human, it will attack. If not, it will leave in a few days.\n\nIf you can capture it, you can study it for dark knowledge.</LetterShamblerArrived>
  <LetterShamblerAnimalsArrived>A group of shambling, rotting {ANIMALKIND_label} corpses is approaching. Some inhuman force has reanimated these lifeless bodies and set them to murder.\n\nThey will now wander through the area. If they see a human, they will attack. If not, they will leave in a few days.\n\nIf you can capture one, you can study it for dark knowledge.</LetterShamblerAnimalsArrived>
  <LetterTextEntityDiscoveryResearch>Your discovery of {ENTITY_definite} has yielded new insights. You can now research the following dark projects</LetterTextEntityDiscoveryResearch>
  <VoidCuriosityText_Researched>{PAWN_nameDef} has begun to fixate on the void, and wishes to investigate it using the void provocation ritual.\n\nUse the void provocation ritual to discover and capture entities. Captured entities can be studied to complete dark research projects, or connected to a bioferrite harvester to generate bioferrite.\n\nPlace a psychic ritual spot to perform the void provocation ritual.</VoidCuriosityText_Researched>
  <VoidCuriosityText_NotResearched>{PAWN_nameDef} has begun to fixate on the void, and wishes to investigate it using the void provocation ritual.\n\nUse the void provocation ritual to discover and capture entities. Captured entities can be studied to complete dark research projects, or connected to a bioferrite harvester to generate bioferrite.\n\nResearch void provocation, then place a psychic ritual spot to perform the ritual.</VoidCuriosityText_NotResearched>
</LanguageData>